So we just arrived in Busan
and we just immediately
checked into our accommodation
which is in Gwangalli beach.
It's a pretty popular location
at least amongst locals here.
And I have to say this is
the prettiest Airbnb accommodation in Busan.
It has a gorgeous gorgeous view
of the Gwangan bridge
which lights up in the evening hours.
I'm going to show you guys later.
I think that if you come to Busan
you really want to at
least stay maybe
either the entire duration or
at least a couple of nights
staying near a beach gives that
sort of essential Busan vibe.
I think most people tend
to drift towards Haundae.
I would arguably say that Gwangalli beach
is the better place to stay in my opinion.
Definitely more the local hot spot.
We decided to stay here
because of the bridge view of course
and this lovely accommodation
that we're gonna enjoy for
the next two nights.
So we're gonna head down
try to find some food.
We're a little bit hungry.
There's a nice little pizza spot that
I've found with a nice beer as well so
yeah looking forward to that.
Let's go.
We just arrived at the SOL Taphouse.
This is a little small pizza joint.
I ordered a beer.
Lisa ordered a cider.
And we just ordered a bunch of
half pizzas.
Place looks really good.
The beer is really good.
So I'm very much
expecting a lot from the pizza.
I'm starving and
can't wait to get started.
Our pizza has arrived.
let's get a bite.
Oh yeah.
Hits the spot.
Just hits the spot.
Just right.
So I should write one to you,
and you will write one to me
Yes.
OK, OK, OK.
I'll write a long message.
It will be sent in 2024.
2024?
By that time, I won't remember
what I wrote to you
That's what makes it fun.
All right, we are on the Blue Line
train or a capsule, sky capsule.
Going at like grandma walking pace,
I would probably call it.
But it provides excellent view of the ocean.
And I would definitely recommend
go from Mipo to Cheongsapo.
That's how you get the ocean view.
You could go the other way of course,
but obviously you're gonna
get blocked by incoming capsules.
It's also a lot less busy
so there's definitely a bigger chance
for you to book a ticket
especially from that direction
compared to Mipo
which is a lot more popular.
And now we're headed to a museum,
an art museum.
Resembles a little bit of teamLab's
digital art displays in Japan.
All right, so we just came out
of the art museum.
It's called Museum One or Won.
That's what it says on Naver,
but I think it's Museum One.
And it was nice.
We were there like
around 10, 11 AM.
There wasn't a lot of people around
so pretty much had the place
almost all to ourselves.
Only a couple of people,
so it was really nice.
But then when we just went outside,
there was like buses
coming in with like kids
and everything like that.
So you wanna go there and get a lot
of nice photo opportunities.
Definitely get here pretty early as
soon as they open, I would say.
But other than that, I
think it was a pretty cool place.
And our bus is coming, I think.
No, it's not.
Maybe?
Okay, it is.
It's not quite what I expected.
I mean, it's okay.
Like, it's not something I would
order every single time I see it, but...
Yeah that's alright.
It's alright.
Trying TAMS...
for the first time...
Mm, it's like Fanta, you know.
It's like Fanta.
It's good, recommended.
You need to go faster.
All right, all right.
So we just went through
the Running Man experience,
and at first I thought it was probably
gonna be a gimmicky kind of thing,
but honestly, I was surprised
how fun it actually was.
We really enjoyed our time.
We were in there for like, what,
two hours or something like that,
and it went by so, so fast.
Yeah, we really wanted to play more,
but we ran out of time.
I definitely recommend it for you guys.
If you're into games
and you have a couple of friends
or with your a close loved
one, definitely just go there
and try it.
It's super fun, totally recommend it.
Nothing feels more like you're in Busan
than eating straight from the grill,
right next to the pavement, basically.
Prices are a little bit
spiked here, I would say.
Definitely an interesting experience.
I think it's worth it
if you're here in Busan.
We are in Jagalchi market.
We just spent...
Half an hour walking around downstairs,
where you see all of
these different fish vendors,
trying to sell you things,
trying to pull you in,
trying to sweet talk you into buying things.
And then after just checking things out,
we decided to head upstairs
where you can find the restaurants,
and this is where you can just go in
and order through like a
a normal menu, basically.
But you could also go
downstairs and buy the fish
and then bring it up
and have these different
restaurants cook it for you.
Now, if you do that,
obviously, it costs a little bit extra,
but if you don't know what you want
and you don't know like how
the dishes gonna come out,
I recommend just
going up to the second floor.
That's where all the restaurants are.
You see a menu, you
can pick out what you want,
it's a little bit cheaper.
But of course,
you don't get that experience
of picking the individual
fish or shellfish that you want.
Me and Lisa just decided to head up
and just look at the menu
We just wanna taste
a little bit of everything,
a little bit of clams,
a little bit of fish.
Lisa been dying
to try a seafood pancake.
So yeah,
our food is about to come.
Is it worth it?
Yes.
This is pretty big.
Looks absolutely delicious,
grilled and everything,
gonna dip it in.